

#### Hardita Kurniawan

Backend developer with 3 years of experience. A fast learner and hardworking person.

Responsibleness on individual or group works. Can adapt to new programming languages quickly and would like to land a challenging position that will expand my learning and build my developer skills.

hardita.kurniawan@gmail.com

+6282233786565

Magelang Regency, Central Java, Indonesia

## **Work Experience**



#### Back End Developer • PT. Dengan Senang Hati

September 2021 - Present

- Create Content Management System to serve as interface for client.
- Collaborate with frontend engineers to ensure website functionality.
- Create a vending machine system and its dashboard.
- Providing API for web-based game using NestJS and MongoDB.
- Developed a web-based multiplayer game campaign in 3 different countries using VueJS and Firebase.



### Junior Web Developer • Indosat Ooredoo

March 2020 - August 2021

- Supported B2B team, monitoring cold chain process.
- Supported in the development of the Digital Ecosystem Platform, designed the Digital Ecosystem Platform business flow based on product owner's needs and requirements.
- Developed B2B web based applications, focused on wrote code, debuged and consumed partner APIs for the desired purpose.
- Participated in developing "Online Single Submission" system by the ministry of BKPM, focused on API integration and web page display using VueJs.



#### Junior Web Developer Internship • Indosat Ooredoo

October 2019 - February 2020

- Developed and maintained corporate web events using Laravel and MySQL as its database.
- Participate in IoT research and development, focus on firmware creation and hardware installation.
- Maker of "Smart Locker" using ESP32 which communicates with smartphone using bluetooth low energy and Firebase as its database.

#### Education



2015 - 2019

#### **Telkom University**

Bachelor's degree , Electrical and Electronics Engineering



2012 - 2015

SMA SEMESTA BILINGUAL BOARDING SCHOOL

Science

## Skills

- Arduino Programming
- PHP
- Laravel
- NodeJS
- Nestjs / TypeScript
- Firebase Realtime Database
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- MariaDB
- JavaScript
- Git

# Languages

• English — Intermediate

Powered by **CakeResume**